CHUNG LAI LEE | JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Location: Manchester mail: <u>cl.lee.ofz@gmail.com</u>

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Junior front end web developer with experience in Agile development. Working knowledge of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, ES6, JQuery, Node.js, ReactJS, APIs, source control, test driven development, and Visual Studio. Experienced in building functional, user friendly apps such as a weather dashboard and a work day scheduler. Possesses right to work in the UK with an excellent standard of written and spoken English. Acquired general business experience within the luxury car industry.

KEY PROJECTS

Multiverse Trump Game | https://github.com/pandi1813/Project---Multiverse-Trumps-Game | https://pandi1813.github.io/Project---Multiverse-Trumps-Game/

- A Top Trumps style game featuring characters from various fictional universes
- Contributed to API sourcing, core features development and document writing as a team member
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API, Bootstrap, DOM, custom fonts

Weather Dashboard | https://github.com/cl-lee/weather-dashboard | https://cl-lee.github.io/weather-dashboard/

- Displays the today's weather and the five days forecast for a selected city
- Responsible for implementing application features and document writing
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API, Bootstrap, DOM

Work Day Scheduler | https://github.com/cl-lee/work-day-scheduler | https://cl-lee.github.io/work-day-scheduler/

- A daily planner application to help one schedule tasks in a day
- Responsible for implementing application features and document writing
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Moment.js, Bootstrap, custom fonts

CAREER SUMMARY

edX United Kingdom

Student - Skills Bootcamp in Front End Web Development

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

Outline

Attendance on an intensive 16-week program focused on web development fundamental and programming skills including HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, ES6, JQuery, Node.js, ReactJS, APIs

Key responsibilities

Utilised acquired knowledge and skills to develop functional, interactive applications

Key achievement/projects

 Created a Top Trumps style game application with teammates in two weeks, achieving 99% score for the project

Proman Supply Chain Limited

Manchester

Despatch/ Hygiene Operative/ Warehouse Operative

Sep 2022 – Nov 2022

Outline

Worked at different client sites, performed various roles as required by clients to help them achieve business goals

Key responsibilities

- Identified different types of products quickly, ensuring that they are distributed to the correct area
- Anticipated teammates' needs, providing assistance where needed while ensuring assigned tasks are completed on time

- Cleaned client sites according to their needs and specification
- Ensured compliance with clients' in-house rules, and health and safety regulations

Achieved 100% production targets using 90% of the allocated time on a consistent basis

Key achievement/projects

Senior Aftersales Administrative Officer

Hong Kong

Oct 2019 - Jun 2022

Provided administrative, data processing and training support for the after sales team at a Mercedes-Benz dealer. Coordinated with stakeholders to facilitate the launch of new products and initiatives

Key responsibilities

Zung Fu Co. Ltd.

- Managed concurrent duties effectively on a daily basis, including but not limited to sales records management, data processing and reporting, customer service, and troubleshooting operations issues
- Coordinated with colleagues and vendors on operations processes and marketing initiatives
- Trained colleagues on tasks, providing written and verbal materials to help them achieve fluency with the process

Key achievement/projects

- Helped the service contracts business generate over one million pounds in annual revenue
- Developed and improved spreadsheets, utilising them to increase efficiency of data reporting and administrative processes by 20%

Aftersales Administrative Officer

Mar 2014 - Sep 2019

Provided administrative, data processing and customer support services to help deliver the best customer experience

Key responsibilities

- Reviewed incoming data, sales order document and marketing materials, ensuring that they are accurate and satisfy business requirements
- Inputted and updated data on the company database swiftly and accurately
- Answered written and verbal customer enquiries to high service standards

Key achievement/projects

Promoted to Senior Aftersales Administrative Officer in 2019

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Social Science, Psychology - National University of Singapore, Singapore